[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Nnngrrrragh!
[announcement klaxons]
PA: Danger.
"Danger"!
PA: High energy exchange detected
in radioactive materials handling bay.
"Radioactive materials".
Oh, Jesus, that just gave me
a horrible thought.
No... no! We can't be
THAT stupid! Please! No!
Oh, this isn't so bad. This column
is clearly waiting for me to pass
THEN it will collapse so I can
die of thirst or starvation.
Maybe I already am and
don't even know it yet.
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO FEED
ME BEES; IT'S NOT THAT BAD!
Okay, can your alien intellect
figure out how doors work?
[metallic thumping]
Oh, they're thinking about it.
Maybe it's too hard for them...
since it's motion-sensored?
Yeah, they couldn't figure it out.
Well, good job trying
to ambush me. Almost.
Hey, I'm getting low on shells
so you know what that means.
[agrunt moans]
Hey, I don't like this
any more than you do.
Rockets for tanks and attack
choppers are no-brainers.
Frankly, it's a bit much for you,
but what am I supposed to do?
I'm low on ammo and you're
running across the room.
Huh, guess I won't die of thirst.
But yeah, what am I supposed to do, go
hand-to-hand with the bodybuilder aliens?
Yeah, that'd be smart, wouldn't it?
I suppose that'd be the
"honorable" thing to do,
but "honor" doesn't really apply to me.
I mean, look at the--
[teleportation sound]
OH MY GOD!
Well, thanks for testing the
tensile strength of the catwalk,
but your services are no longer required.
Yeah, just ignore gunfire.
That works for me.
Wow!
All right, so I guess the aliens have lowered
their standards for shock troopers.
I mean, that alien was obviously high.
He falls off a ledge.
He doesn't care, he's high.
I shoot him in the head.
He's a galactic stoner.
But yeah, while the resource
allocation DOES concern me,
I'm not going to lose sleep over bringing
a rocket launcher to a bee fight.
Umm...
[straining]
Okay, maybe this does something.
Yeah... the thing is, fighting honorably
and winning are incompatible goals.
In World War II, the Japanese
TRIED to do it honorably
but even they knew it
wasn't going to work.
Like, when they hit Pearl Harbor.
The idea...
...come on...
The idea was attacking the USA
unaware would be dishonorable,
so they tried warning us half an
hour before it happened,
but their military delayed that message
until 20 minutes AFTER it happened.
Fuck!
So, I guess they kept their
honor on a technicality?
Like the ball was on the goal line and
there were three seconds left on the clock,
therefore the Pearl Harbor attack
was honorable or something?
Yeah, what the hell am I talking
about? This is my last pistol magazine.
Of course I used the right weapon!
More guns, less madness.
Okay, what's the story on this guy?
Did he blow his brains out?
I hope he left some bullets behind.
But, it's hard to say; knowing our staff,
he probably missed a few times
trying to aim for his head.
No, I don't see anything.
Okay, another pump. I was trying
not to think about this.
I don't exactly know what this switch
does, but I need to pull it right now,
because if I'm wrong, I made some parts
move around and some lights flash,
doesn't matter.
But, if I'm right about this...
Oh my God!
Being right about everything is a curse!
Let's look at the evidence:
we have a staff member getting
snippy with me about a reactor;
we have that intercom talking
about biological contaminants;
we have those red pump warning lights;
and we have the building
literally falling apart.
I think we have a nuclear reactor
down here, an alien teleported inside it,
now it's broken,
and is going to meltdown unless
I flood it with coolant.
I mean, somebody tell me I'm wrong,
that a team of top researchers
are not so tragically obtuse
that we pass off a fucking China syndrome
as just "one of those things"!
The scientist trying to give me
orders was slightly annoyed.
He wasn't somber or panicked at all.
Yeah, a meltdown IS really
annoying. I get it!
I think I'm the only person here who
understands how serious this is.
I hope I'm wrong, but this is
all too plausible.
Even though we have a dam, we
use as much power as a city.
I can believe we have a nuclear
reactor here also.
Plus, these are my colleagues who
thought sealing off the entrance
would contain random teleportations.
They drew straws to decide
who would let me in.
Now that I am in, I'm sure the prevailing
theory being discussed behind my back
is that all these aliens just showed up
during the two minutes they left
the door open and I walked in.
This is my fault. Of course.
I know what's happening here.
I've seen this a hundred times.
This reeks of groupthink.
You have one normally brilliant
person make a stupid decision
and everyone else just falls in
line, doesn't question anything.
These people aren't scientists;
they're cultists with advanced degrees.
I guess I'll go talk to the reactor guy,
find out just how long we have to live.
SHOW ME YOUR HANDS OR I'LL
BLOW YOUR FUCKING HEAD OFF!
Yeah, try me, psycho-breath!
GUARD: Our luck has to
change sooner or later.
What's THAT supposed to mean?!
NO, DON'T ANSWER THAT!
I'M NOT LETTING YOU GET INSIDE MY MIND!
Fucking psycho Kurtz
serial-killing security guard...
Hey, we need to talk!
SCIENTIST: Don't linger Mr. Freeman!
You've turned on the pumps!
SCIENTIST: Now take the access
pipe, flood the core,
SCIENTIST: and get on up to the
labs without delay!
Oh, so NOW you're talking like
there's some urgency.
The ramifications are
starting to sink in, huh?
Well, I saved your ass.
And everyone else's.
If you clowns had just said the
word "meltdown",
we could've saved a lot of time.
Your communication skills are horrible.
I swear, I'm the only person in this
building who's not an idiot savant.
PA: Lambda Complex reports
dimensional contamination.
"Dimensional"...
GUARD: What the hell is this?
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS, POP TART?!
IT'S ME POINTING A 12-GAUGE AT YOUR FACE!
You may think you're hard because
you plugged a scared old man,
but try that number on me and
watch what happens!
I didn't come all this way just
to get shot in the back of the head
by some bored rent-a-cop.
If the ninjas took me out, there
would at least be some dignity to that.
With you, there's nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
Okay, is this the reactor?
IS YOUR NAME "REACTOR"?!
HEY, THIS IS A MISUNDERSTANDING!
JESUS!
I'M NOT EVEN SURE I HAVE THE RIGHT ROOM!
AAAH!
[gun clicks]
DAMMIT, I'M OUT!
HI!
HOW ARE YOU NOT--
Good God! I didn't realize the aliens
made this their bathhouse!
[hivehand firing]
AAAAH!
WHAT THE FUCK?!
YOU WEREN'T THERE AND NOW YOU'RE REAL!
THIS IS INNSBRUCK ALL OVER AGAIN!
GO! BACK! TO NOTHING!
THAT'S WHERE YOU BELONG!
Okay, I'm going to stay in my corner.
Then, to sneak up on me, you have to
teleport into a wall, so fuck you!
You know what the difference is between
my hallucinations and other people's?
My hallucinations shoot back at
me and kill other people.